to quickly go through the basic
understanding of React and JavaScript so
they could understand what the...
The.
Whatever AI model then we use to come up
with that particular code app,
they will be able to understand what is
happening where. So,
the basic understanding of React and
JavaScript is required. So, JavaScript,
they have, they have JavaScript exposure.
Can you check my code,
but I'm not giving say yes, lot of them,
most of them are.
Yeah,
most of them are heavily doing cameras,
right? So, but that's what we can take.
No, what is that? So,
what are the what's the TG and what is
the target? Well, that's my thing. So,
who are we giving this? No,
first we have to make sure that it is
done to a set of people.
OK, not defining that it is A or BT or B,
you know, this similar or table.
We are just making this to see that first,
across the organization,
if we need to understand the skill set,
it's mandatory, then we need to do it,
but...
Priority, we want to,
because is already required to, so,
so even with priority,
they would be downstream, maybe we have.
What?
But you have to 1st understand the gap
from a moderating point of view.
That is why I must say this. So,
the gap point of view,
what are the gap we can tell by people?
Fundamentals required and what is not
there.
Required fundamental, so it's ABC.
What is not there today?
That is the first thing which may be a
fail, see?
I know Microsoft has got a thing,
but I realized that even if we tell him
to do that, that's not so.
Divya.
They would still get an understanding of
it,
but the problem to resolve will still be
in, because, for sure, personal hands on,
some of them from, like,
if let's say you are taking it for them,
they will come up in,
I know the person is giving me this
particular post, so when it's hands on,
will...
Like, so I could,
it would be more effective.
Yeah, I learned because, so,
and Microsoft learned because see,
there's already this quarter happening,
like there's a team that's,
so he was particularly, of course,
and it's quite slow because there is,
it's they are,
they are posted it themselves, right?
And if it is in one,
if there is one person giving that same
phone.
It's A hands-on, I think.
That's a problem.
Right, so you take.
Ajit.
What are the skills,
which is a gap for us? So, fundamentals,
looks like let's finish that,
and what are something that you can just
draw it out there before you go into this,
like you both can actually tell what the
fundamental which is required to be done,
like these are, we may need, yeah,
we still really get off any of this.
We would we could focus on React,
because that's more publicly,
but when you're writing an option,
what are the fundamental options?
Essentially, if we do,
if we check the whole overview,
just JavaScript is required,
because React functions on JavaScript,
so if you know how things work with
JavaScript,
then you would have some understanding.
Can we, I know that it's not just React,
can we know any of these things?
Microsoft didn't say anything.
Why I am discussing with you,
it should be easier for somebody to
switch and then,
if you have done and done this way.
So, is React this way,
or is it do the rest way,
or is there anything else?
What is similar to Power FX? Nothing,
Power FX is,
and what is similar to the way of
development,
like I think first they create components,
and then can I can you start the whole
leave behind all of this React use
component based development?
Yeah,
so first you generalize and build the
components that you can reuse up with the
application for. OK, it's not.
So, I am,
I'm not a person who says that we react,
because we are,
we should not be ourselves bad,
so if rules are better option, OK,
or any other framework,
because operating framework can be
anything.
See, because we react, react,
we speak every day,
or if we have time somebody speaking,
we say react,
that's the reason why we say react,
we don't need to say react,
if somebody can ask another skill set.
OK, I'm just documenting reactors more,
right?
There's a lot of more documentation,
I believe, is there.
We agree, I agree, we are very popular,
so who is very popular,
who is very popular,
but who came out later,
so Nayak came out first,
so we have so very more easier and more.
Friendly for good signals, and it's basic.
That's what I agree to,
so I'm not debating here,
but I just want you guys to all to take
leaders,
but you guys need to think that they are
taking a strategy of saying, "Okay,
we're not primarily with react or
primarily with or any other platforms
already a limitation."
Because it will support,
and and why we do all of those things is
one of the reasons, right?
And we are actually using all of these
front end frameworks is also a reason is
the main reason why people are going to
board Akshay.
But we need to do a basic understanding
of JavaScript.
So that is required for everyone to know.
They know HTM and CSS very well.
Fundamental to me is that CHTM with CSS
and JavaScript.
Then only comes the framework.
It will be translated.
But then framework is required,
but if you don't know HTML, CSS,
JavaScript,
you can't do React or can't do the other
one.
Because its all bad.
But, you, you, I, I am sorry to say, sir,
but what I am thinking is,
if that would take time for us,
for people around us, I mean, everybody,
to come up to an understanding where all
of this basically works with them,
so if they are going to go through and
HTML.
The whole of CSS,
let's say basic understanding,
so basic understanding is fine. So,
how can you be? Well,
now you write down these points: HCML,
CSS, JavaScript.
JavaScript, let's say React,
you put React this much, right? No, no,
below, below,
below that you put React also,
React as a framework,
because that's a common framework does
React in this case, now in this.
You take, let's say, marketing.
How will somebody,
how good is somebody like uh,
or somebody like uh,
Vishruth or Jeevan during the ask?
How do you make that?
Okay.
So, you tried on top, identifying who is,
I'm not really identifying. Yes,
take a guess. I don't go and ask,
how good are you?
It's a very subjective answer, right?
Rather,
we just take that subjective decision
ourselves.
Do you think that they know CSS?
Do they know JavaScript?
You can ask them this question, sir.
There's nothing else. HTML can ask them,
they won't know,
but serious and react is rather,
so then our trainees should actually have
those. That is what I was trying to.
You should be, you got the reason. See,
I know we also should press a training
plan,
but what is required for our team is what
we are trying to say, in our team,
because within when I ask within to do
training on successes.
What are we getting on time?
I just spelled out one small. I asked,
we tried too much JavaScript training,
or it's here in training by it's here.
Yeah, even all of us.
You getting one, BS?
I, I don't want to waste your time,
because you are not the expert on those
areas, right? So, I mean,
somebody come back to do a session,
but what should I,
how we make sure that you know they are
actually good?
The fact that the entire team needs that
training,
or are there just few of them who need it,
so, so...
Continuation to this point,
whether Rigu is going to HTML,
whether she's done any CSS by herself,
whether she knows JavaScript,
has she done any kind of JavaScript
validation, you know,
calling a function or calling an API,
you know, these kind of things,
has she done?
I think that's a question, but exactly,
so question.
But I can take him.
I, Claude, or something,
we have been doing this.
We need to fix it or to understand the
timing.
That is the concern that we are really
trying to enable them to that level.
We're not trying them to build them as an
expert. The moment they go,
they know how to go on to Claude and ask
them.
They already gave me a code to build it.
That is the second part of it.
So,
I'm not trying to bring up to a level
finding,
give a basic overview of HTML CSS,
so that they get, you know,
session on here, so maybe.
In other ways, what is the use of AI?
You don't have to go to the one number on
train, there is still a lot of time.
Give them up to speed with the day
sponsors, and then close it, and then.
Using part to us with this data,
by the time we can look at the further
plan and see if there are,
so this is the part two of the plan.
Pretty good, that's how it looks like,
because we haven't get this right,
so do you have any of these things
currently on this thing?
Let's go to the next one.
You must have considered,
I want to see these fundamentals of this,
right? Yeah.
So, you need to do that, right? Yes,
what is this? Let's just do that, yes,
sir, for all the people,
so that we can tell you that now,
any program, what you're gonna do,
then you have to ask.
Hmm, understood.
Yes, sir. So,
what do you address the next slide?
They're going practical,
but trying to what it makes in use case
also.
So.
Build the four practical capabilities.
So what a developer in the end needs to
understand and do is basically read and
run the application,
use the real data contract.
So basically whatever Microsoft code app,
whatever.
the sample template that is present,
right?
So we are basically creating a copy of it.
So we have a basic skeleton of how it is.
And then we are trying to add in the data
sources that are present that we create
in Dataverse or SharePoint,
whatever it is, add that into the data.
The space template that we created with
Microsoft different templates that have
available,
and then direct AI to basically go
through this project folder and
understand what is the requirement,
so the requirement is to be explained by
us to them, I mean to AI.
so that it gets a picture on what has to
be done.
And then once it generates a particular,
generates the output based on our
requirement and the file structure that
is present,
we have to review it and understand that
it is functioning correctly,
working correctly.
And if there is a concern,
either fix it manually or...
with the help of that AI order we chose
to deploy with all of them.
The what?
No,
this is what the basic 4 fundamentals
that a developer needs to have to.
We don't know what you mean.
So a basic,
so when you create a particular project,
right, there'll be different structures,
substructures, subfolders, components,
and all of that inside a particular
format structure.
So a developer needs to understand what a
particular section of a project is,
what each file is, how it works,
so that they get an idea of where a
particular.
part of an application is present rather
than having always going to a AI model to
understand, okay, what is this?
Where is this? How do I fix this?
They need to know an understanding of how
this app is, where each of it is located,
and how that functioning is present.
Use real data contact. So basically,
over here in this context,
I use this dataverse, but...
The data platform that we choose could be
either SharePoint or Dataverse,
depending upon what the business needs.
So we are basically...
So, that is not automatically,
so we uh Power Apps CLA, right?
They we have a...
function call that we can do.
It's called PA app in it and once you do
that,
you need to initialize a power config
file that is present in a particular
folder that maps the environment,
application name, application ID,
all of that together.
Then you add data sources into that
particular folder structure,
I mean folder that we created for the
project. So that is PA.
I,
there's no different commands available.
They never responded.
Yeah, no, what I'm saying is,
when you're trying to develop an
application, we need to know,
in this case,
in React or whatever the platform mean
framework is,
we need the model and services that
interact with this particular data model
that we're using,
so we need to define that, I mean,
create that into this particular project
directory.
We can't clear the comments.
No, but each particular branch, each,
I'm saying it is done automatically.
We don't have to do it.
We don't have to set up manually.
Once you initialize a particular command
and provide which table details that you
require,
which table that you want in this
particular solution, I mean project,
it automatically picks up the particular
table, create the data layers for it.
So it creates a model and a service for
it.
So model contains all of your table
structure,
and the service contains the different
functions that you can call for the table.
So that setup is done automatically by
your function call.
We don't have to manually create data
results and forecasts.
Once that particular model, that is,
we are not doing anything.
So when you do that particular,
so once you run a particular command,
let's say in this case,
PA add data source, let's say user table.
So that user table gets added to the
particular project that we are referring
to.
And that creates its own generated folder,
which contains the.
user tables model and user table service.
So we have these two files.
So me as a developer,
I need to know that what happens in these
files, what is present in these files,
and how can I use these files.
Send more than services for this.
Yeah.
Okay, once then direct and review AI.
So I need to understand, basically,
I need to know what is a business
requirement,
what the business requires to be done in
the application. And I need to...
Make sure that particular AI model that
I'm instructing to create this particular
application, right?
It needs to know exactly what my
requirement is, so what, but why,
what is that here? No, but it is needed,
so...
You prompting is needs to be right is
what I'm saying,
because if prompt goes wrong,
you could create an application,
but that is not what the user wanted in
the end.
Correct,
but that element should be actually the
prompting.
The first round would be the ones that
are the most important,
because that's because the first round,
if it is deviated or if it is already
made from,
it would add that is actually part of the
that process of development itself, right?
Well, requirement, you can create that,
yes,
so automatically we do all the separation,
but you are using it to automatically do
that, right? So, no, no,
I'm saying before it does all of this
automatically,
we need to make sure that what
instructions being given to the model is
correct. Can you develop this outside,
like in Corex or...
Yeah, these things are very useful.
I think it you not call me then the whole
development.
Other than BS code on VS code, there is,
yeah,
since talking about directly in products,
or in or for any directly for products
application,
like if you want Java application,
you can actually do it in products, right?
I mean, we just got an ID. Let's see that,
so...
Can you do a code apps development
outside VS code apps development?
I'm not sure. Where do you develop? Sorry,
where do you develop a code app Visual
Studio? Yeah, okay.
Have you done it on VS Code and then used
VS Code, VS Code?
This, of course, no, please,
for any questions, otherwise, please,
not I.D.
You mean directly ask a model to do it
and not give a practical session on chat,
you?
It wouldn't want to stand on very many
application, tell the requirements, say,
I want business as a so-and-so
application, it will build that, well,
it will actually build that.
Okay.
In in that tool, it doesn't need this,
so for four apps,
is it mandatory that you need to have
this tool? That is my first question.
If you ask me personally, yes,
it is required because you letting AI
model to completely do a whole project.
And then...
Yeah, OK. Good time.
The export pass through other things
which we installed for.
See,
and all of those things that he would
input store,
but there is another platform,
how does it actually handle?
She said she would need a node.
js that he can, so the question is,
other tools develop the AI tools,
can we do this? Like, we have no, we have,
yeah, basically saying,
ask a particular AI model correctly.
To create the application,
don't involve VS.
Code or any other ID to it. Now,
what if that plot chat or that GPT chat
has access to your data?
It would create CW,
it would create a data report,
that same data report you put in the
share and commanding for it.
It becomes a code.
You just ask, let's say Claude,
to go and find the code app data repo.
It will clone that data repo first in a
cloud,
so the cloud place that would sit
somewhere in one of a repo that it
creates in your data.
That's also possible.
I think.
To check that out, can't really,
so that's one that works, so I'm not sure,
let's see what are the next side.
Is what the plan is to make sure
everybody gets a hands-on on it.
There was a five-hour training for one
day; it's not really a training,
as per se, but rather,
then one of the big day, 8 hours,
so 8 hours, I'll count to that. OK, OK,
OK, yeah, next one,
missing the point in that. OK, OK.
Case, what, what is this?
This is an application that we think of
for...
For developers to create,
so very basic application,
basic for use case.
VS.
Thanks.
OK, that's it. OK,
so this one help us use case helps to
plan, but we go to, yeah, second of site.
This one, yeah.
Once in another four days,
we can't stack this.
OK, right,
because we have to fix that in two
developments. One is, like we said,
requests to be required for somebody to
include actual development.
OK, that's OK. OK, then.
When you spoke of our data.
How do you access these apps?
It's an important part.
How do you development with prompting is
also another thing which I'm seeing as an
important thing, which platform how?
It actually works out to reach me.
Right,
so that structure should be structured to
handle. This won't be the point. OK, OK,
OK. This will not help them to scale.
Firstly, fix them.
Then we do your reimbursement data itself.
There's no problem,
but reimbursement also,
you should actually tell what somebody
should actually build.
Together.
In the,
it cannot be like the open number in this
thing.
You want to do with prompt and the same,
right? You see, you know...
You say it's clearly defined on, yeah,
that's why I'm not speaking on with the
screenshot, technically, nothing else,
like our structure.
They should not be wasting time.
They should clearly look at what they
should actually problem with that and how
quickly they can actually build is what
we are actually trying to.
So along with this,
I think we need to add even the prompt.
I can add it in the requirement for the
use case, but training should not be this.
Training should be.
Yes, well done.
That is right.
I will say that, OK. See,
they just do something without
understanding over there.
So, like this one, that is what I thought,
like this thought, it doesn't it, it, it,
it connects with your use case activity,
no matter the use case,
they weren't able to.
So, how do you start a project?
How do you define the environments?
What are the preinquisites which has
required for you to run it on the new
school, deployment strategy?
How do you connect to a database,
like Dataverse, right?
Is your data doing data from the machine,
right?
How do you integrate this with data?
So,
all those things should be the training
structure, and it is,
you can't expect the how we connect to be
in a lower session, no,
they said 5 minutes, right?
But that should be the activity which is
to be, rather than, yeah, actually.
With dealing with HTML, CSS,
we will now have another session.
It made them before in this thing, right?
And one exercise for them to do CSS.
One minute, so let them understand,
know how we actually responded,
this is what we're going.
You, you want a question? Yes,
otherwise it will not be helpful for the
developer.
That is what I am trying to see again.
Okay. Last part is already fine,
but from last part,
you actually add two bits,
a requirement document and the UI.
Well, that collapsed. Sorry, it was,
that's fine.
At the prompt and other things,
creating the game rules and all those
things, when she refined it with them,
use that to create it.
We need to check into that,
because super man,
we just tell that Copilot could do it,
which GitHub Copilot and do what your
data was, and...
VS code development.
It, it could, it could,
it could link it up. Yeah,
we were asking you whether I got
something directly or not.
That is a different question.
They don't write about it;
it has to be developed about it,
but we're not, we have to do.
This is not exercise queue to understand
the quality of the problem,
it is an enablement.
On this, yeah,
so we don't we don't focus on that;
we focus on the learning, they can.
Got it.
OK, yes.
So, what is the action?
We will get back to you in first,
find out the strengths and what are the
strengths and we can,
if there are more things we can do. Okay,
we have something.
I love to fill it in the next 10 minutes.
Or, if you can put a poll in one of these,
let's see here.
So,
once we get a basic understanding of how
where everybody is at, I think,
based on that, we can create a plan,
and then we'll get back to you on it.
close it, man.
Now we know what we're doing,
spend another one hour, finish,
close it today,
but what we need to know needs to be this.
That is good.
Something like.
Okay, I think it's good.
So action item is this. Yeah.
You will refine that for slagging your
children.
Features or fundamentals and code
actually,
which needs to be developed as a sequence.
This is to do fundamentals that is
required, how to set up a project,
how to use data layer,
and then how to develop using React,
what what does it actually recover?
Right, so Rex one session,
JavaScript session, we get the blue one.
Sachin on Deepak.
OK, so that one thing you, yeah,
I think that's for that,
even if I show you,
and the other one is separate,
see that I'm not even worried,
you share that,
we can really create that requirement,
right, give a UI from that.
Then we do the very important.
The technician.
Ohh,
I created some something called an AI
like where I...